{"deck":{"1":{"name":"1","front":"timestamp format","back":"YYYYMMDDHHMMSS","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 10:31:17 -0600","interval":2400},"2":{"name":"2","front":"What does t refer to in the migrate Class block?","back":"Within the block t refers to a TableDefinition object but we can just think of it as the table being created in the database","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 10:31:21 -0600","interval":2400},"3":{"name":"3","front":"What is the name of the arguments passed in a migrate Class block? And what do they do?","back":"Constraints. They keep our code clean","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"4":{"name":"4","front":"How does a class get sweet methods to do migration (schema/table) stuff?","back":"Inherits from ActiveRecord::Migraion","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"5":{"name":"5","front":"Is an ID required to migrate?","back":"No, itâ€™s automatically created","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"6":{"name":"6","front":"What is the expression to add a timestamp inside the migration block?","back":"t.timestamps where t is the iterator","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"7":{"name":"7","front":"What are the optional columns that add additional features?","back":"created_at - Automatically gets set to the current date and time when the record is first created","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"8":{"name":"8","front":"How can you override an existing class table name / column for the primary key / class name?","back":"self.table_name = new name\n self.fixture_class\n self.primary_key = product key","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"9":{"name":"9","front":"Whats the difference between new and create","back":"New creates a new object","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"10":{"name":"10","front":"Which method to access the entire collection of that object?","back":"all","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"11":{"name":"11","front":"Which method to return the first of the collection?","back":"first","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"12":{"name":"12","front":"Which method to search the collection for the first occurrence of an attribute? Syntax?","back":"find_by","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:40:01 -0600","interval":1200},"Card1":{"name":"Card1","front":"this is the front","back":"this is the back","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 09:01:10 -0600","interval":4800},"card2":{"name":"card2","front":"front2","back":"back2","last_reviewed":"2015-11-12 07:30:13 -0600","interval":600},"card3":{"name":"card3","front":"front3","back":"back3","last_reviewed":"2015-11-11 20:54:59 -0600","interval":4800},"card4":{"name":"card4","front":"front4","back":"back4","last_reviewed":"2015-11-11 20:55:00 -0600","interval":4800},"card5":{"name":"card5","front":"front5","back":"back5","last_reviewed":"2015-11-11 20:55:02 -0600","interval":4800}}}